Register to The David Stanley Smith Papers
Yale University Library
- Memorabilia, VIII
  - Memorabilia 1917-1952, 7 + 17 items. (Box 40, Folder 1-2)
Prelude, choral and fugue, organ, orchestra, op. 10 Solo Keyboard
Prelude, organ Keyboard
Prelude, postlude, and offertory, organ Keyboard
Prelude - sudden storm Keyboard
Prince Hal Orchestral
Prince Hal, op. 31 Orchestral Orchestral
Promenade Chamber
Psalm 145 Choral
Quartet, strings, op. 19, E minor Chamber
Quartet, strings, op. 2, C minor Chamber Chamber
Quartet, strings, op. 37, A major Chamber
Quartet, strings, op. 46, C minor Chamber
Quartet, strings, op. 57, E flat Chamber
Quartet, strings, op. 62, D major Chamber Chamber
Quartet, strings, op. 71, C Chamber Chamber
Quartet, strings, op. 74, D minor Chamber
Quartet, strings, op. 77, A Chamber
Quartet, strings, op. 80, B flat Chamber
Quartet, strings, op. 90, A Chamber Chamber
Quartets, string Chamber
Quintet, piano, strings, op. 56, E flat Chamber
Rachel Songs
Requiem, violin, orchestra, op. 81 Solo Chamber
Rhapsody of St. Bernard Choral Choral Choral Choral
Rhesus Opera
The rising of the storm Songs
The rising storm Songs
Robin of Sherwood Opera
Roll out, o song to God Songs
Romance Misc
Romany love-song Songs
Romanza for violin Misc
Rondo appassionato, violin, orchestra, op. 73 Solo Solo Chamber
Roof-tops Songs
The rose Songs Songs
The rose is weeping for her love Songs
Rose song Songs Songs
Russet lawns and fallows gray Keyboard
Russian carols Misc
Ruth Songs
Sailing boats Songs
The scarecrow Songs
Scenes from tragedy, violin, piano, op. 67 Chamber
Scherzo for band Band
Scherzo for organ Keyboard
Send forth thy light Choral
Serenade Songs Songs Misc
Seven years old Songs
Sextet, strings, op. 63, D minor Chamber Chamber
She walks in beauty Misc
The shepherd queen Songs Songs
Shepherds idyl Orchestral
Sinfonietta, string orchestra, op. 65, no. 1 Orchestral Orchestral Keyboard
Sing we Noël once more Misc Misc
Sixth Ohio Misc
The sleeping priestess Choral Choral
Slumbersong Songs
So sweet is she Songs Songs
Sonata, 2 violins, op. 91 Chamber
Sonata a Due Voci Chamber
Sonata, clarinet, piano, op. 84 Chamber
Sonata in G minor Misc
Sonata No. 1 in A flat Keyboard
Sonata, oboe, piano, op. 43 Chamber
Sonata pastorale Chamber
Sonata, piano, D Keyboard
Sonata, piano, op. 61, A flat Keyboard
Sonata pour violon et piano Misc
Sonata, viola, piano, op. 72 Chamber Chamber
Sonata, violin, piano Chamber
Sonata, violin, piano, op. 51, A Chamber
Sonata, violin, piano, op. 93, D Chamber
Sonata, violin, piano, op. 96, D minor Chamber
Sonata, violin, violoncello, op. 68 Chamber Chamber
Sonata, violoncello, piano, op. 59 Chamber
Sonatina, string orchestra, op. 65, no. 2 Orchestral
A song of the four seasons Songs
Songs Songs
Songs of three ages Songs Songs
Songs, op. 15 Songs Songs Songs
Songs, op. 18 Songs Songs Songs
Songs, op. 22 Songs
Songs, op. 29 Songs Songs Songs
Songs, op. 3 Songs Songs Songs
Songs, op. 33 Songs Songs Songs
Songs, op. 45 Songs Songs
Songs, op. 53 Songs Songs
Still, still within Thee Songs
String quartet no. 6 Chamber
Suite, piano, op. 25 Keyboard
Summer winds Choral Choral
Sursum corda Keyboard
Sweet Clementine Songs
Sympathy Songs
Symphonic adagio Misc
Symphonic ballad, orchestra, op. 24 Orchestral
Symphony in miniature, op. 49 Orchestral
Symphony, no. 1, op. 28, F minor Orchestral
Symphony, no. 2, op. 42, D major Orchestral
Symphony, no. 3, op. 60, C minor Orchestral
Symphony, no. 4, op. 78, D minor Orchestral Keyboard
Symphony, no. 5, op. 99, E flat Orchestral Orchestral Orchestral Keyboard
Symphony, op. 9, C minor Orchestral
Tattered classics Misc
Te Deum laudamus Choral Choral
Tears Songs Songs
Tempo de valse Misc
Ten provençal carols Misc
Theme, variations and finale, piano, op. 100 Keyboard
There will be stars Songs Songs
Three songs to texts by Laudor Songs
Time: five-four Chamber
To Etta Songs
Tomorrow Orchestral
Tomorrow - an overture. Orchestral
Tomorrow, orchestra, op. 66, no. 2 Orchestral Orchestral
Touchdown two step Misc
Tragic prelude, violin, piano, op. 41 bis Chamber
The Transfiguration Songs
Trio, piano, strings, op. 16, G major Chamber
Trio, piano, strings, op. 44, C major Chamber
Triumph and peace, organ, op. 88 Keyboard
Troilus and Cressida Opera
The Trojan women Opera
Two pieces for concert band Band
Pieces, violin, piano, op. 96 bis Chamber
La vie est brève Songs
Vienna invicta, orchestra, op. 85 Orchestral
The vision of Isaiah Choral Choral
Waltz Misc
A wanderer's psalm Misc
When stars are in the quiet skies Songs Songs
When the wind Songs
When winds are raging Songs
Why so pale and wan? Choral
Wind and autumn leaves Keyboard
The wind-swept wheat Choral Choral Choral
"Yale '99" march Misc
Yale pageant, 1916 Choral Choral
Yesterday and Tomorrow Orchestral
The zíncal Choral